Finding aid for Department of Afroamerican and African Studies (University of Michigan) records, 1966-2010 (bulk 1970-1994)
Bentley Historical Library
- Audio recordings on cassettes, 1975-2001
  - Graduate Student Conference [became Student of Color of Rackham (SCOR]
    - Otto Gonzalez, John Stiles, Gracia Clark & Keletso Atkins: Session 2A: To Be a Colonial: Life in a Colonial and Post-Colonial World, 1991 February 02; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Session 2A; To Be A Colonial, Life in a Colonial and Post-Colonial World; Presenters: Otto Gonzalez, Natural Resources;
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-292-1]
    - Otto Gonzalez, John Stiles, Gracia Clark & Keletso Atkins: Session 2A: To Be a Colonial: Life in a Colonial and Post-Colonial World, 1991 February 02; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Session 2A; To Be A Colonial, Life in a Colonial and Post-Colonial World; Presenters: Otto Gonzalez, Natural Resources; "Third World Threatened by a New World in 1992"; John Stiles, Anthropology; "Revolutionary Logic, Republican Myth, Politics, Culture and Assimilation in the Departmentalization of the French Antilles"; Discussants, Assistant Professor Garcia Clark, CAAS, Anthropology; Assistant Professor Kelesto Atkins, CAAS, History) (Box 32)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-293-1]
    - Raynal Harris, Eric Porter, Valerie Sweeney Prince, Nancy Cho & Jimmie L. Reeves: Session 1: Negotiations of Culture: Aesthetic, Spatial and Textual, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Raynal Harris, Eric Porter, Valerie Sweeney Prince; Chair: Nancy Cho, Discussant: Jimmie L. Reeves.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-294-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-294-2]
    - Raynal Harris, Eric Porter, Valerie Sweeney Prince, Nancy Cho & Jimmie L. Reeves: Session 1: Negotiations of Culture: Aesthetic, Spatial and Textual, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Raynal Harris, Eric Porter, Valerie Sweeney Prince; Chair: Nancy Cho, Discussant: Jimmie L. Reeves.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-295-1]
    - Gina Barclay-McLaughlin, Petula Brown, Pamela Joshi, Lynetta Mosby, Shilpa Dave & Donald R. Deskins, Jr.: Session 2: Racial Equity and Public Policy, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Gina Barclay-McLaughlin, Petula Brown, Pamela Joshi, Lynetta Mosby; Chair: Shilpa Dave; Discussant: Donald R. Deskins, Jr.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-296-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-296-2]
    - Gina Barclay-McLaughlin, Petula Brown, Pamela Joshi, Lynetta Mosby, Shilpa Dave & Donald R. Deskins, Jr.: Session 2: Racial Equity and Public Policy, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Gina Barclay-McLaughlin, Petula Brown, Pamela Joshi, Lynetta Mosby; Chair: Shilpa Dave; Discussant: Donald R. Deskins, Jr.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-297-1]
    - Laurent Dubois, Jean M. Leverich, Beth Notar, Natalie Bennett & Simon Gikandi: Session 3: Race and National Identity: Beyond the United States, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; [Panelists:] Laurent Dubois, Jean M. Leverich, Beth Notar; Chair: Natalie Bennett; Discussant: Simon Gikandi.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-298-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-298-2]
    - Laurent Dubois, Jean M. Leverich, Beth Notar, Natalie Bennett & Simon Gikandi: Session 3: Race and National Identity: Beyond the United States, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Panelists: Laurent Dubois, Jean M. Leverich, Beth Notar; Chair: Natalie Bennett; Discussant: Simon Gikandi.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-299-1]
    - Michele Tracy Berger, Susan Edwards and Susan Jenkins: Session 4: "I See, Therefore You Are?" The Body, the Gaze and the Self, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Michele Tracy Berger, Susan Edwards and Susan Jenkins; Chair: Tamara Duckworth; Discussant: Patricia Smith Yaeger.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-300-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-300-2]
    - Michele Tracy Berger, Susan Edwards and Susan Jenkins: Session 4: "I See, Therefore You Are?" The Body, the Gaze and the Self, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Panelists: Michele Tracy Berger, Susan Edwards and Susan Jenkins; Chair: Tamara Duckworth; Discussant: Patricia Smith Yaeger.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-301-1]
    - Natasha Barnes, Bill Tivenan and Valerie Nao Yoshimura: Session 5: "Things ain't change, they just rearrange": Gender and racial metamorphoses, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Natasha Barnes, Bill Tivenan and Valerie Nao Yoshimura.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-302-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-302-2]
    - Natasha Barnes, Bill Tivenan and Valerie Nao Yoshimura: Session 5: "Things ain't change, they just rearrange": Gender and racial metamorphoses, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Panelists: Natasha Barnes, Bill Tivenan and Valerie Nao Yoshimura.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-303-1]
    - Ana M. Biaz, Joseph Dorsey, Nancy Hopkins Donnell Walton, Max Weintraub, Rama Sethi and Dorceta Taylor: Session 6: Activism and agitation: The role of science and economics in social change, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Ana M. Biaz, Joseph Dorsey, Nancy Hopkins Donnell Walton, Max Weintraub; Chair: Rama Sethi; Discussant: Dorceta Taylor.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-304-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-304-2]
    - Ana M. Biaz, Joseph Dorsey, Nancy Hopkins Donnell Walton, Max Weintraub, Rama Sethi and Dorceta Taylor: Session 6: Activism and agitation: The role of science and economics in social change, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Panelists: Ana M. Biaz, Joseph Dorsey, Nancy Hopkins Donnell Walton, Max Weintraub; Chair: Rama Sethi; Discussant: Dorceta Taylor.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-305-1]
    - Lynn Perry, Erika Hayes, Jocelyn Finley-Nickelson, Stacy Blake, Yvonne "Baubie" Paschal and Alfred L. Edwards: Session 7: Workforce 2000: Managing beyond black and white in corporate America, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Lynn Perry, Erika Hayes, Jocelyn Finley-Nickelson, Stacy Blake; Chair: Yvonne "Baubie" Paschal; Discussant: Alfred L. Edwards.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-306-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-306-2]
    - Lynn Perry, Erika Hayes, Jocelyn Finley-Nickelson, Stacy Blake, Yvonne "Baubie" Paschal and Alfred L. Edwards: Session 7: Workforce 2000: Managing beyond black and white in corporate America, 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Panelists: Lynn Perry, Erika Hayes, Jocelyn Finley-Nickelson, Stacy Blake; Chair: Yvonne "Baubie" Paschal; Discussant: Alfred L. Edwards.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-307-1]
    - Heidi Ardizzone, Miriam Duchess Harris, Grace yoon-aie Pang, Frances Rivera and Earl Lewis: Session 8: Race and National Identity: Considerations of America(ness), 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Panelists: Heidi Ardizzone, Miriam Duchess Harris, Grace Yoon-aie Pang; Chair: Frances Rivera; Discussant: Earl Lewis.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-308-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-308-2]
    - Heidi Ardizzone, Miriam Duchess Harris, Grace yoon-aie Pang, Frances Rivera and Earl Lewis: Session 8: Race and National Identity: Considerations of America(ness), 1993 February 04; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Q&A Session.; Panelists: Heidi Ardizzone, Miriam Duchess Harris, Grace Yoon-aie Pang; Chair: Frances Rivera; Discussant:Earl Lewis.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-309-1]
  - Barbados
    - Stanley Greaves, 1989 May 15; audiocassette; (This side is the first part of the lecture; Stanley Greaves lecturing on the subject of art, language, and diversity in Barbados.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-310-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-310-2]
    - Jocelyn Massiah, 1989 May 15; audiocassette; (Jocelyn Massiah discussing the demographics, women, and gender in the Caribbean.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-311-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-311-2]
    - George Lamming, 2012 May 16; audiocassette; (Tape 1 of 2; Lecture and reading by George Lamming, writer from Barbados.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-312-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-312-2]
    - George Lamming, 2012 May 16; audiocassette; (Tape 2 of 2; Lecture and reading by George Lamming, writer from Barbados.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-313-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-313-2]
    - Aggrey Brown, 1989 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Lecture by Aggrey Brown, director of the Caribbean Institute of Mass Communication.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-314-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-314-2]
    - Aggrey Brown, 1989 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Lecture by Aggrey Brown, director of the Caribbean Institute of Mass Communication. [Side 1 was blank]) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-315-1]
    - Ricky Singh, 1989 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 1 of 2; Lecture by Ricky Singh, journalist from Barbados.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-316-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-316-2]
    - Ricky Singh, 1989 May 17; audiocassette; (Tape 2 of 2; Lecture by Ricky Singh, journalist from Barbados.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-317-1]
    - Kathleen Drayton, 1989 May 18; audiocassette; (Tape 1 of 2; Lecture by Kathleen Drayton, Caribbean artist and playwright.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-318-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-318-2]
    - Kathleen Drayton, 1989 May 18; audiocassette; (Tape 2 of 2; Lecture by Kathleen Drayton, Caribbean artist and playwright.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-319-1]
    - Hilary Beckles, 1989 May 19; audiocassette; (Part 2; Lecture by Hilary Beckles, Barbadian historian and academic.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-320-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-320-2]
    - Hilary Beckles, 1989 May 19; audiocassette; (Part 4; Lecture by Hilary Beckles, Barbadian historian and academic.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-321-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-321-2]
    - Dorbrene O'Marde, 1989 May 22; audiocassette; (Tape 1 of 2; Calypso music playing throughout, lecture by Dorbrene O'Marde.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-323-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-323-2]
    - Dorbrene O'Marde, 1989 May 22; audiocassette; (Tape 2 of 2; Calypso music playing throughout, lecture by Dorbrene O'Marde.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-324-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-324-2]
    - Roderick Rainford and Peggy Antrobus, 1989 May 22; audiocassette; (Tape 1 of 3; Peggy Antrobus begins her lecture on CARICOM and women's movements in the Caribbean.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-325-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-325-2]
    - Peggy Antrobus, 1989 May 22; audiocassette; (Tape 2 of 3; Peggy Antrobu lecture on CARICOM and women's movements in the Caribbean.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-326-1]
    - Peggy Antrobus, 1989 May 22; audiocassette; (Tape 3 of 3; Peggy Antrobu lecture on CARICOM and women's movements in the Caribbean.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-327-1]
    - Vanda Radzig, 1989 May 22; audiocassette; (Tape 1 of 2; Lecture by Vanda Radzig discussing Frantz Fanon.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-328-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-328-2]
    - Vanda Radzig, 1989 May 22; audiocassette; (Tape 2 of 2; Lecture by Vanda Radzig discussing Frantz Fanon.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-329-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-329-2]
    - Lemuel Johnson, 1989 May 24; audiocassette; (Lecture and discussion by Lemuel Johnson on the Barbadian Study Abroad.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-330-1]
  - Martin Luther King Day
    - Bennet: Tribute to Dr. Martin Luther King, 1987 January 17; audiocassette; (Recording of the Tribute to Dr. Martin Luther King with music, speeches, and hymns.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-331-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-331-2]
    - Charles Moody and Lemuel A. Johnson: Moody: A Celebration of Our Interconnectedness; Johnson: The Changing Forms of Racism: Historical and Current Perspectives, 1988 January 18; audiocassette; (Faculty Senate Assembly Meeting; Dr. Lemuel A. Johnson, The Changing Forms of Racism: Historical and Current Prospectives; Rackham Amphitheater) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-332-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-332-2]
    - Ruby Dee and Ossie Davis: Tribute to King, 1988 January 18; audiocassette; (Recording unintelligible. Low quality recording.] A series of speeches in tribute to Martin Luther King.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-333-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-333-2]
    - Ernest Wilson and Omari Kokole: MLK Lecture, 1988 January 18; audiocassette; (Speeches by Ernest Wilson and Omari Kokole commemorating Martin Luther King Day.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-334-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-334-2]
    - Omari Kokole and Barbara Ransby: MLK Day, 1988 January 18; audiocassette; (Tape 1 of 2; Speeches by Omari Kokole and Barbara Ransby commemorating Martin Luther King Day.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-335-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-335-2]
    - Omari Kokole and Barbara Ransby: MLK Day, 1988 January 18; audiocassette; (Tape 2 of 2; Speeches by Omari Kokole and Barbara Ransby commemorating Martin Luther King Day.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-336-1]
    - Frank Ellis: Dreams and accomplishments: The tortuous path to achieving equity in the health care system, 1988 January 19; audiocassette; (Sponsored by the School of Public Health, Public Health Students of African Decent.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-337-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-337-2]
    - Robert Christman: Martin Luther King Day, 1989 January 16; audiocassette; (University of Michigan "Diversity Day"; Robert Christman, Editor "Black Scholar"Introduction by Prof. Lemuel Johnson - (Director of the Center.)) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-338-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-338-2]
    - Artists for Cultural Equity: I, too, Sing America, 1990 January 15; audiocassette; (University of Michigan Artists for Cultural Equity presents in honor of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Recital Hall, 2:30 pm; U-M School of Music (Program at MLK Day 1990 Blacks at U-M File).) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-339-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-339-2]
    - Haki Madhabuti: MLK Day, 1990 January 15; audiocassette; (Haki Madhabuti speaking on the commenoration of Martin Luther King Jr. Day.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-340-1]
    - Earl Lewis, Rebecca Scott and Martha Norman: Race, Social Change and the Search for Power, 1990 January 15; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Department of History Symposium entitled "Race, Social Change and the Search for Power.") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-341-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-341-2]
    - Earl Lewis, Rebecca Scott and Martha Norman: Race, Social Change and the Search for Power, 1990 January 15; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Department of History Symposium entitled "Race, Social Change and the Search for Power.") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-342-1]
    - Ethnic Issues in the Media, 1991 January 21; audiocassette; (1-2:30pm; Bill Johnson, editorial board for the Detroit News, speaking on "Ethnic Issues in the Media.") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-343-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-343-2]
    - Michael Blakely: Struggle for Human Rights, 1991 January 21; audiocassette; (Lecture by Michael Blakely entitled "Struggle for Human Rights.") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-344-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-344-2]
    - James Forman: Civil Rights Movement in the 1950s and 1960s, 1991 January 21; audiocassette; (Speaker: Dr. James Forman, Civil Rights Leader, and former head of the Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee.) (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-345-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-345-2]
    - Leith Mullins: MLK Day, 1991 January 21; audiocassette; (Tape 1; Lecture by Professor Leith Mullins entitled "Martin Luther King Jr. Day.") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-346-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-346-2]
    - Leith Mullins: MLK Day, 1991 January 21; audiocassette; (Tape 2; Lecture by Professor Leith Mullins entitled "Martin Luther King Jr. Day.") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-347-1]
    - Benjamin Hooks: The Significance of Martin Luther King Day, 1992 January 20; audiocassette; (School of Business; Lecture by Benjamin Hooks entitled "The Significance of Martin Luther King Jr. Day.") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-348-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-348-2]
    - Haki R. Madhubuti: The New Black Nationalism, 1992 January 20; audiocassette; (MLB Aud #3 3-5pm; Black Student Union. Lecture by Haki R. Madhubuti entitled "The New Black Nationalism.") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-349-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-349-2]
    - Anthony Ingram: The Commitments of Leadership, 1992 January 20; audiocassette; (Lecture by Anthony Ingram entitled "The Commitments of Leadership") (Box 33)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-350-1]
  - CAAS Mini-course 324: Black Educational Achievement over the Life-Course
    - Margaret Beale Spencer: The preschool and early childhood years, 1988 March 03; audiocassette; (The Preschool and Early Childhood Years: "Cognition, Identity, and Social Development of Black Children's Academic Skills." Dr. Margaret Beale Spencer - Associate Professor of Educational Studies; Emory University.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-351-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-351-2]
    - Margaret Beale Spencer: The preschool and early childhood years, 1988 March 03; audiocassette; (The Preschool and Early Childhood Years: "Cognition, Identity, and Social Development of Black Children's Academic Skills." Dr. Margaret Beale Spencer - Associate Professor of Educational Studies; Emory University.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-352-1]
    - Reginald Clark: Family life and school achievement: Why poor Black children succeed or fail, 1988 March 10; audiocassette; (Place: The Univ. of Michigan, Ann Arbor, Michigan; Auditorium B, Angell Hall; Introduction: Dr. Walter Allen (Prof. for course), Mr. Richard, Graduate Student.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-353-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-353-2]
    - Bruce Hare: The Middle School or Junior High Years, 1988 March 17; audiocassette; (Part 1; Tape 1 of 4; Speaks on "Structural Inequality, Education Disadvantages and the Endangered Status of Black Youth"; 140 Lorch Hall.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-354-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-354-2]
    - Bruce Hare: The Middle School or Junior High Years, 1988 March 17; audiocassette; (Part 2; Tape 2 of 4; Speaks on "Structural Inequality, Education Disadvantages and the Endangered Status of Black Youth"; 140 Lorch Hall.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-355-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-355-2]
    - Bruce Hare: The Middle School or Junior High Years, 1988 March 17; audiocassette; (Part 2; Tape 3 of 4; Speaks on "Structural Inequality, Education Disadvantages and the Endangered Status of Black Youth"; 140 Lorch Hall.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-356-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-356-2]
    - Bruce Hare: The Middle School or Junior High Years, circa 1988 March 17; audiocassette; (Part 2; Tape 4 of 4; Speaks on "Structural Inequality, Education Disadvantages and the Endangered Status of Black Youth"; 140 Lorch Hall.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-357-1]
    - Edgar G. Epps: The Senior High Years: Correlates of Academic Achievement Among Black Youth in America, 1988 March 24; audiocassette; (Martin Luther King/Rosa Parks/Caesar Chavez Visiting Professors Program. 4-6 p.m.m 140 Lorch Hall) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-358-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-358-2]
    - Walter Allen: Institutional context, interpersonal relationships, personality orientation and black student academic achievement in college, 1988 March 31; audiocassette; (Part 1; Dr. Walter Allen; "Institutional context, Interpersonal Relationships Personality Orientation and Black Student Academic Achievement in College") (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-359-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-359-2]
    - Vincent P. Franklin: The talented tenth: Afro-American Intellectuals in the Twentieth Century, 1988 April 14; audiocassette; (Part 1; Dr. Vincent P. Franklin (The Graduate of Professional Years); Sponsored by: Martin Luther King/Rosa Parks/ Caesar Chavez, 140 Lorch Hall.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-360-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-360-2]
    - Vincent P. Franklin: The talented tenth: Afro-American Intellectuals in the Twentieth Century, 1988 April 14; audiocassette; (Part 2; Dr. Vincent P. Franklin (The Graduate of Professional Years); Sponsored by: Martin Luther King/Rosa Parks/ Caesar Chavez; 140 Lorch Hall.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-361-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-361-2]
  - Chronological events
    - Eunice Royster: What's Unique about Black Leadership, 1983 July 01; audiocassette; (Includes remarks from President of NARSE, Marvin Greene.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-362-1]
    - Walter R. Allen, Masipula Sithole, David Gordon, Sulayman Nyang, Ron Walters and Ali A. Mazrui: Reflections on Ali Marui's 'The Africans' TV Series, 1986 December 04; audiocassette; (Sponsored by CAAS + Rackham. Held in Rackham Amphitheater, 4 Panelists Responding 1. Introductions - Prof. Walter R. Allen, Assoc. Prof. of Sociology and Center for Afro American + African Studies; 2. Masipula Sithole - U of Zimbabwe 3. David Gordon Michigan State Univ. + Research Assoc, CRED - UMichigan; 4. Sulayman Nyang - Howard University, African Studies; 5. Ron Waters, Howard U.; Ali A. Mazrui - Prof. Political Science + CAAS U-M, + Professionships at U of Jos + Cornell.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-363-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-363-2]
    - Ali Mazrui: Africa's Triple Heritage, 1986 November 21; audiocassette; (Tape is sped up; content is difficult to hear]) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-364-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-364-2]
    - Ted Sevransky: Racial Jokes, 1987 February 04; audiocassette; (Only first 10 minutes contain WJJX broadcast, rest of the tape is about a Nursing Home] Part 1 and 2.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-365-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-365-2]
    - Michael Dawkins: Michael Dawson, 1987 February 04; audiocassette; (Michael Dawson chairing a symposium entitled "Black Support for the Presidency.") (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-366-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-366-2]
    - John Behee: Black Lettermen Athletes of U-M, 1987 February 13; audiocassette; (Dr. John Behee, Prof. of Physical Education, Alumnus of University of Michigan, Author of Hail to the Victors: Black Lettermen Athletes of UM. Friday 1:15-3pm; Rackham Auditorium.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-367-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-367-2]
    - Jon Onye Lockard: An African Journey, 1987 February 24; audiocassette; (General Presentation; "An African Journey"; A multimedia presentation of an Afroamerican pilgrimage through the Diaspora with music, dance, song and slides; Narrator: Jon Onye Lockard.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-368-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-368-2]
    - State Representative Morris Hood: Hood Hearings, 1987 March 04; audiocassette; (Part 1; Morris Hood chairing a hearing on the racist WJJX radio broadcasts.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-369-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-369-2]
    - State Representative Morris Hood: Hood Hearings, 1987 March 04; audiocassette; (Part 2; Morris Hood chairing a hearing on the racist WJJX radio broadcasts.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-370-1]
      - [side 2], [2012140-SR-370-2]
    - State Representative Morris Hood: Hood Hearings, 1987 March 04; audiocassette; (Part 3; Morris Hood chairing a hearing on the racist WJJX radio broadcasts.) (Box 34)
      - [side 1], [2012140-SR-371-1]